Guide to the Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project records
2001-2006
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5571
5571-001
Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project
0.71 cubic feet 1 box
DVD listening copies of oral history interviews done as part of the Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project between 2001 and 2006
The Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project, based at the University of Washington under the direction of Professor James Gregory, is a multi-media website dedicated to documenting the Pacific Northwest’s multiracial labor and civil rights history. It offers over 1000 primary documents and photographs, over 70 video oral histories, original research essays produced by undergraduate and graduate students, short films, slideshows, historical overviews and bibliographic guides. The project is a rich web-based resource designed to provide teachers, students, community members and researchers with information about Washington’s past.
This collection contains 90 DVD listening copies, in 75 cases, of oral history interviews done by UW Professor of History, James N. Gregory, graduate student Trevor Griffey, and others, as part of the Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project, between 2001 and 2006.
Open to all users. Until January 1, 2025, these recordings are Library Use Only. No copying is permitted for any purpose except with permission of Professor James N. Gregory or the Chair of the Harry Bridges Center for Labor Studies.
These audio DVDs are listening copies only. The originals remain in the possession of James N. Gregory.
Source: James N. Gregory, August 24, 2009
The visual materials that form part of this collection are described and indexed in
A Guide to the
.
See the Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project at http://depts.washington.edu/civilr/
Seattle Civil Rights and Labor History Project$vArchives; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington)
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Colleges and Universities; Civil Rights; Labor History; Oral Histories; Electronic Records; Sound Recordings
- By Interviewee
  Arranged alphabetically
  - Acevez, Pedro: Interview by Oscar Rosales, Edgar Flores, 01/27/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Adams, John: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Janet Jones, 06/24/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Alexander, Belle: Interview by Sarah Miner and James Gregory, 05/03/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Amen-Allah, Keuyatto: Interview by Janet Jones, 8/02/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Bacho, Peter: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 10/28/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Bill, Willard: Interview by Teresa Powers, 2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Bocanegra, Juan Jose: Interview by Chris Paredes, Cristal Barragan and Trevor Griffey, 02/02/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - CAMP, 40th Anniversary, 10/28/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Carver, Vivian: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 02/24/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Chew, Ron: Interview by James Gregory and Trevor Griffey, 12/15/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Chin, Doug: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Brooke Clark, 03/01/20005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Close, Dan: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 05/08/2004 (Box-folder 1)
  - Cook, Mark: Interview by Janet Jones, 05/28/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Seattle CORE, Joan Singler, Betty Lou Valentine and Jeane "Maid" Adams, discs 1 & 2: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Jim Gregory, 10/06/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Cornish, Megan, discs 1 & 2: Interview by Nicole Grant, 10/20/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Della, David: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Lindsay Park, 11/08/2004 (Box-folder 1)
  - Diaz, Antonio: Interview by Edgar Flores, 10/12/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Dixon, Aaron, discs 1 & 2: Interviews by Janet Jones and Trevor Griffey, and Janet Jones and Alex Morrow, 05/02/2005, 07/13/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Dixon, Elmer: Interview by Janet Jones and Trevor Griffey, 05/17/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Dixon, Michael, discs 1 & 2: Interviews by Janet Jones, 06/27/2005, 08/10/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Domingo, Lynn: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 11/23/2004 (Box-folder 1)
  - Domingo, Nemesio: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Jennifer Taylor, 12/08/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Durham, Heidi: Interview by Nicloe Grant and Trevor Griffey, 11/07/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Fidder, Jake: Interview by Janet Jones, 06/04/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Fox, Michael, discs 1 & 2: Interviews by Trevor Griffey, 05/19/2004, 03/10/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Gallegos, Sidney: Interview by Edgar Flores, 06/05/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Gamboa, Erasmo: Interview by Angelita Chavez and Trevor Griffey, 11/01/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Gossett, Larry, discs 1 & 2: Interviews by Trevor Griffey and Brooke Clark, and Trevor Griffey, 03/16/2005, 06/03/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Guillen, Rosalinda: Interview by Sharon Walker, 03/12/2004 (Box-folder 1)
  - Hayasaka, Phil: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Morgan Banks, 12/06/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Hobbs, Leon: Interview by Janet Jones and Trevor Griffey, 05/09/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Hollingsworth, Dorothy: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 03/16/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Hubbard, Walter, discs 1 & 2: Interviews by Trevor Griffey and Brooke Clarke, and Trevor Griffey, 02/17/2005, 06/21/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Irigon, Francisco: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Meg Elston, 11/23/2004 (Box-folder 1)
  - Johnson, Charles: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Brooke Clark, 03/03/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Johnson, Doug, IBEW #46: Interview by Nicole Grant and Trevor Griffey, 06/19/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Johnson, Ron: Interview by Janet Jones and Trevor Griffey, 07/29/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Kato, Charles: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Simeon Man, 04/16/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - King, Ivan, discs 1 & 2: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 05/25/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Lewis, Janet: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Nicole Grant, 04/13/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Lewis, Randy: Interview by Lossom Allen and Trevor Griffey, 04/18/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Lowry, Mike: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 04/19/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Maeda, Sharon: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 12/30/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Maestas, Roberto: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 02/22/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Martinez, Frank & Blanca Estel: Interview by Oscar Rosales, 06/24/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Martinez, Ricardo, judge: Interview by Edgar Flores and Oscar Rosales, undated (Box-folder 1)
  - Matsuda, Larry: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 11/03/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - McKinney, Samuel, reverend: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 03/16/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Mercer, Lyle: Interview by Daren Salter and Trevor Griffey, 08/15/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Murray, Mike: Interview by Janet Jones, 05/31/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Orange, Tony: Interview by Tikia Gilbert, Trevor Griffey and Janet Jones, 11/16/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Owens, Gary: Interview by Janet Jones, 11/26/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Parrey, Will & Louise, discs 1 & 2: Interview by Ducher Ko, 03/06/2002 (Box-folder 1)
  - Redress Conference, discs 1 & 2, 04/28/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Redress Conference, discs 3 & 4, 04/28/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Richardson, Larry: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 06/16/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Riojas, Rogelio: Interview by Michael Castenada, Francesca Barajas and Trevor Griffey, 01/19/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Rodriguez, Jesus, discs 1 & 2: Interviews by Trevor Griffey and Monica Perez, and Roberto Alviso and Cristal Barragan, 03/03/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Ross, Michael: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 01/28/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Saldana, Rebecca: Interview by Angelita Chavez and Alex Morrow, 09/15/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Santos, Bob: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 11/12/2004 (Box-folder 1)
  - Simmons, Fred: Interview by Nicole Grant and Trevor Griffey, 05/15/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Sims, Beverly: Interview by Nicole Grant and Trevor Griffey, 05/25/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Smith, Charles Z.: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 04/14/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Spence-Lewis, Infanta: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 11/20/2006 (Box-folder 1)
  - Sugiyama, Alan, discs 1 & 2: Interviews by Trevor Griffey and Jennifer Speidel, and Sarah Minor and Trevor Griffey, 11/16/2004, 11/02/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Tagawa, Mike, discs 1 & 2: Interviews by Janet Jones, and Trevor Griffey, 06/02/2005, 11/08/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Uhlman, Wes: Interview by Janet Jones and James Gregory, 08/25/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Velona, Velma: Interview by Trevor Griffey and Stephanie Johnson, 10/26/2004 (Box-folder 1)
  - Villanueva, Tomas: Interview by Anne O'Neill, 04/11/2003 (Box-folder 1)
  - West, Jim: Interview by Gordaon Black, 04/08/2002 (Box-folder 1)
  - West, Marion: Interview by Trevor Griffey, 06/21/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - Williams, Shamseddin: Interview by Janet Jones and Alex Morrow, 07/13/2005 (Box-folder 1)
  - White, Bobby: Interview by Janet Jones, undated (Box-folder 1)
  - Woo, Michael: Interview by Nicole Grant and Trevor Griffey, 12/30/2005 (Box-folder 1)